looxcie.com 2014-02-14

# Privacy Policy - Looxcie

**Effective: October 2011**   Thank you for using the services available through the Looxcie mobile application and the website at the domain name Looxcie.com, each, that are provided by Looxcie, Inc. (the“Looxcie Service”). At Looxcie, we strive to make your online experience with us secure and satisfying. This Privacy Notice describes and governs what information we gather from you, how we use that information, and what we do to protect it. By using the Looxcie Service, you expressly consent to the information handling practices described in this Policy. If you do not want information about you to be used in the manner set forth in this Privacy Notice, please do not use the Looxcie Service. This Privacy Notice is expressly incorporated into our Terms of Use. Your use of the Looxcie Service and any personal information you provide through the Looxcie Service are subject to this Privacy Notice and the Terms of Use at all times. 

## Changes and Updates

  We may periodically revise this Privacy Notice. Please revisit this page to stay current with any changes. The most recent version of this Policy will always be available on the Looxcie Service. The effective date of any changes will be posted at the top of this page. For changes to this Privacy Notice that may be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of personal information you have provided to us, we will attempt to obtain your consent before implementing the change. Your continued use of the Looxcie Service constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Notice and any future revisions. 

## Information Looxcie Collects

  Looxcie collects two types of data about users: (1) information that you or others voluntarily submit to us (described below under“User-Supplied Information”) and (2) technical data automatically collected from all visitors to the Looxcie Service (described below under“Automatically Collected Data”). **User-Supplied Information:** In using the Looxcie Service, for example when you create an account with us, or if you send us an email, you will provide Looxcie with data generally called “personally identifiable” information. If you choose to provide such information, you are giving Looxcie permission to use and store that information consistent with this policy. Additionally, please know that when you create an account or sign in to the Looxcie Service, you are not anonymous to us. 

  1. **Mobile device information:** We may store your phone number, as well as information regarding your mobile device, including your mobile phone number, device type and operating system and information in your mobile phone’s address book or in other applications as permitted by the functionality of such mobile device.
  2. **Profile Information:** To create an account for the Looxcie Service, you will need to provide access to the information on your Facebook account through Facebook Connect. By doing so, you understand and authorize us to use all the information exposed to us through Facebook Connect pursuant to this Privacy Notice, including your status updates, photos, videos, name, email address and information regarding your friends on Facebook. You should check your Facebook settings to change the information sent to us through Facebook Connect.
  3. **Location:** You may allow the Looxcie mobile application to have access to your location to provide helpful information and services based on where you are located (i.e., by allowing your mobile device to send us your location).

**Automatically Collected Data:** The Looxcie Service operating on a website automatically logs non-personally identifiable information such as Internet Protocol address (“IP Address”), a unique user ID, the content and pages that you access on the Looxcie Service and the dates and times that you visit the Looxcie Service. In addition, if you come to the Looxcie Service via a link from another site, we may also track the source of that link. **Information Regarding “Cookies”:** Like many other websites, the Looxcie Service may send one or more cookies – small text files containing a string of alphanumeric characters– to your computer. Looxcie may use cookies to track user traffic patterns as described above. Looxcie may use both session cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie disappears after you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Looxcie Service. Persistent cookies can be removed. You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser, however, some features on the Looxcie Service may not function properly if your cookies are disabled. Please review your web browser “Help” file to modify your cookie settings. 

## Information we Obtain from Other Sources.

We may collect information about you from other sources, including from partners, and from commercially available sources (such as data aggregators and public databases). The following are examples of information we may collect from other sources: Data you authorize us to access through your use of Facebook Connect. In general, the types and amount of personally identifiable information we collect vary depending on the activity. Looxcie endeavors to limit the collection of personally identifiable information to information we believe is minimally necessary to achieve our stated collection purposes. 

## The Way Looxcie Uses Information

Looxcie uses personally identifiable information to establish and enhance our relationship with you. Looxcie may use the information that you provide, or that we collect, to operate, maintain, enhance, and deliver the various features and services found on the Looxcie Service; as well as to track user-generated content and users to comply as a service provider with the DMCA and other applicable laws. Looxcie uses all of the information that we collect from users to understand and analyze the usage trends and preferences of our users, to improve the way the Looxcie Service works and looks, and to create new features and functionality.Further, Looxcie may use automatically collected data to: (a) remember your information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit Looxcie; (b) monitor your participation in various sections of the Looxcie Service; (c) customize our service to you, including by providing you with recommendations and (c) monitor aggregate site usage metrics such as total number of visitors and pages viewed. We may use your e-mail address for administrative communications such as notifying you of major Looxcie Service updates, for customer service purposes, and to send privacy or security-related notices. 

## How Looxcie May Disclose Information

Looxcie does not share your personally identifiable information with other organizations for their marketing or promotional uses without your prior consent. We may share your personally identifiable information with companies that provide services to us, including outside vendors, contractors, or agents who help us manage our business activities. Such entities only use your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Notice and for no other purpose than to provide us with necessary services. Looxcie may disclose personally identifiable information if required to do so by law or under the good faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws (including, without limitation, U.S. copyright or trademark laws) or respond to a court order, subpoena, judicial or other governmental requirement or warrant in a manner required by the requesting entity. Looxcie also reserves the right to disclose personally identifiable information that we believe, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to take precautions against liability; enforce our Terms of Use; protect Looxcie from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful uses; to initiate, render, bill and collect for amounts owed to Looxcie; to investigate and defend ourselves against third-party claims or allegations; to assist government enforcement agencies; to protect the security or integrity of the Looxcie Service; or to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Looxcie, our Users, or others. In the event that Looxcie is acquired by, merged with, or our assets are transferred to, another entity, such entity may be able to use your personal information under the terms of this Privacy Notice. 

## Access to Your Personal Information

If you create an account as a member of Looxcie, you may update, correct, or delete your profile information and preferences at any time by e-mailing us at privacy@Looxcie.com. To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you account access or making corrections to your information. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information at all times. 

## Children

Looxcie does not knowingly collect or retain personally identifiable information about persons under 13 years of age. Any person who provides their personal information to Looxcie through this website represents that they are 13 years of age or older. If Looxcie learns that personally identifiable information of persons under the age of 13 years has been collected on the Looxcie Service without verifiable parental consent, then Looxcie will take the appropriate steps to delete this information. If you are a parent or guardian and discover that your child under the age of 13 has obtained a Looxcie Service account, then you may alert Looxcie at privacy@Looxcie.com and request that Looxcie delete that child’s personal information from its systems. 

## Data Security

Looxcie uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. However, no data transmissions over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. We cannot, therefore, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Looxcie, and you do so at your own risk. Please know that although we make our best efforts to keep your information secure, this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. If Looxcie learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. By using this website or providing personal information to us you agree that we can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy and administrative issues relating to your use of this website. Looxcie may post a notice on the Looxcie Service if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free written notice of a security breach, or to opt out of receiving electronic notice you should notify us at privacy@Looxcie.com. 

## International Visitors

The Looxcie Service is hosted in the United States. If you visit the Looxcie Service from the European Union or other regions of the world with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from laws of the United States, then please understand that you are transferring your personally identifiable information outside of those jurisdictions to the United States for the uses identified above in accordance with this Privacy Notice. By providing your personally identifiable information on the Looxcie Service you consent to that transfer. 

## Third Parties

Except as expressly provided otherwise, this document addresses only the use and disclosure of information that the Looxcie Service collects from you or that you disclose to us. If you disclose your information to others besides Looxcie different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. Looxcie does not control the privacy policies of third parties, and you are subject to the privacy policies of those third parties where applicable. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others. 

## Contact

Please contact Looxcie with any questions or comments about this Privacy Notice, your personal information, our third-party disclosure practices, or your consent choices by e-mail at privacy@Looxcie.com or by mail at Looxcie Inc., Attn: PRIVACY NOTICE.
